theysmell.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - 730 Sage Street

## 730 Sage Street Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy for the web site 730 Sage Street (https://www.730sagestreet.com).

Our postal address is:  **P.O. Box 401; Lowell, IN 46356**

We can be reached via e-mail at: 730sagestreet@gmail.com

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name, IP and e-mail address (if entered).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who comment on the blog, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

With respect to cookies: As most blogs do, we use cookies to store visitors preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit and stats. We currently rely on the stats of Google Analytics. We may change which counter we use, but all collect cookies.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. **We will only email you let you know about upcoming promotions and to email you back when you leave a comment on our blog in response.**

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. You will need to check their sites for their privacy information. We use Google Adsense and Adthrive.

**From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.** If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries).

Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have factual inaccuracies corrected in information that we maintain about them.

This site frequently posts promotional content or affiliate links.  This content may have been sponsored and compensated in some form.  Opinions expressed are that of the site owner.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information in this privacy policy, you may contact us at the above email address.
